playboost.com 2011-10-07

# Playboost

Updated September 9, 2010 

Thank you for visiting playboost.com (the "Site"). The Site is an Internet property of Playboost Media Inc. and its affiliated companies ("Playboost", "we" or "us"). This privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") outlines the privacy practices associated with the Site. You agree to this Privacy Policy, in its entirety, when you: (a) access or use the Site; and (b) agree to receive e-mail from us via the Site, or any other means. 

Please be advised that Playboost may not itself provide all the featured products or services, or any other related products and services available through the Site. The Terms and Conditions and Privacy Policy of any featured products and/or services provided by any third party providers will be determined by those third party providers and it is your responsibility to review and accept those agreements prior to your access and use of such websites. We will collect your email address if provided by you for value added services that are provided by us through the Site. We will use your email to send you reminders for certain events and dates that you have identified through your account settings. If you no longer wish to receive email reminders, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each reminder email sent by us or contact us at [privacy@playboost.com](mailto:privacy@playboost.com). 

### Information Collected

We will not facilitate the collection of your personally identifiable information if you do not complete the applicable registration process in full. The types of personally identifiable information that we collect at the Site may include, without limitation, your: (a) first name and last name; (b) e-mail address; and (c) any and all other information requested on the applicable registration form. Should you need to update/remove any of the personally identifiable information that you have submitted through the Site, you will need to contact us at [privacy@playboost.com](mailto:privacy@playboost.com). We will use your email to send you information about products and services we feel will be of interest to you. If you no longer wish to receive our promotional e-mails, please follow the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional e-mail. In addition, if you opt-in to receive special offers from our trusted third party companies, we will share your e-mail address with them for this purpose. To change your sharing preferences, please contact us at [privacy@playboost.com](mailto:privacy@playboost.com). To unsubscribe from any third party e-mails, please contact the applicable third party company directly. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about you when you visit many of the pages of the Site. This non-personally identifiable information includes, without limitation, the type of browser that you use (e.g., Internet Explorer, Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome), your IP address, the type of operating system that you use (e.g., Windows or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of the Site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze Site usage, as well as to offer you products and services. We also reserve the right to use aggregate or group data about our visitors for any and all lawful purposes. Aggregate or group data is data that describes the demographics, usage and/or characteristics of our visitors as a group. 

### Blogs, Forums and Chatrooms

If you use a blog or any other form of communication medium on this Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for any information you choose to submit in these communication forums. 

### Third-Party Offers

Playboost provides its users with the opportunity to receive special offers, products and/or services from third parties. Where you indicate the desire to receive certain offers, products or services from a third party during the applicable information collection process, your personally identifiable information that was provided during that Playboost information collection process will be shared with the applicable third party so that such third party may provide their product or service to you and so that you do not have to complete another information collection form to purchase or receive that product or service. Playboost does not store any personally identifiable information that you submit in order to receive such offers from third parties. 

### Cookies

When an end-user visits the Site, we send a cookie and/or gif file ("Cookie") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to the applicable end-user's Internet browser. A Cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing non-personally identifiable information about you. Cookies have many benefits to enhance your experience at the Site. To disable and reject certain Cookies, follow the instructions associated with your Internet browser. Even in the case where a user rejects a Cookie, he or she may still use this Site. Send Interactive reserves the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely. We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and web beacons to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors and site visitation to our site in the aggregate. 

### Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

When you submit your information through the Site, you have opted-in to receive information and communications from us. To opt-out of having future email communications from us, please contact [privacy@playboost.com](mailto:privacy@playboost.com) or follow the opt-out request process in the applicable email communication. 

### Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to change, modify, add and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice to you. Notice regarding any Privacy Policy changes will be placed in a prominent location on the Site and will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check the Site periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of any and all changes. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us at: 

Playboost Media Inc.  
201-1221 Broad St  
Victoria, BC, V8W 2A4  
Canada
